piccing.com 2018-01-01

# Privacy Policy - The Piccing Blog

## **Our Policy:**

Welcome to piccing.com (the “Site”) of Piccing, Inc. (“Piccing”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). The Site is operated by Piccing and has been created to provide information about our company and to provide you with information about our Site, our application for mobile devices (the “App”) and the services we offer (the “Services”) to our Site visitors and/or App users ( collectively, “you”, “your”). This Privacy Policy sets forth Piccing’s policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from Site visitors and/or App users.

**Information We Collect:  
**  
When you interact with us through the Site and/or the App, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

Personal Data That You Provide Through the Site and/or the App: We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, register for access to the Services or use certain Services. Wherever Piccing collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy.  
By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to the Site, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Piccing and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States and outside of the United States.

**Other Information:  
**  
Non-Identifiable Data: When you interact with Piccing through the Site and/or the App, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Piccing may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Piccing affiliates, agents or service providers. The Site and/or the App may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers, and the total number of downloads of the App. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.

In operating the Site, we may use a technology called “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Site gives to your browser when you access the Site. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. For instance, our Site may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Site without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Site. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Site’s features.

Aggregated Personal Data: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, Piccing often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Piccing may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Piccing may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

**Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information:  
**  
Piccing uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by e-mail, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Piccing and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Piccing Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Site and/or the App to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site and the App, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. Piccing and its affiliates may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

If Piccing intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

**Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:  
**  
Piccing is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. Related Companies: We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy. Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: Piccing, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another Service to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

Legal Requirements: Piccing may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Piccing, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

**Exclusions:  
**  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Piccing other than Personal Data collected through the Site and/or App. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Piccing through the Site, the App, or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as boards (collectively, “Public Areas”), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Piccing shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

**Children:  
**  
Piccing does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Site. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on the Site without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Piccing through the Site, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

**Links to Other Web Sites:  
**  
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site and the App. The Site and/or the App may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Piccing (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Site or through the App do not imply that Piccing endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

**Social Media:  
**  
Through the Site and/or the App, you can choose to access certain social media websites and services that are owned and/or controlled by third parties (including, without limitation, Facebook and Twitter) (such websites and services, collectively, the “Social Media Services”). When you elect to access and use the Social Media Services, you will be sharing your information (which will include personal information if you elect to share such information) with those Social Media Services. As with other Third Party Sites, the information that you share with the Social Media Services will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of service of the providers of such Social Media Services and not by the polices and procedures we describe here. You may also be able to modify your privacy settings with these Social Media Services to, for example, control what information the Social Media Services disclose to other entities, including Piccing. When you add Social Media Service accounts to the Services or log into the Site or the App using your Social Media Services account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Site and the App to access that Social Media Service, however you will provide your login information, like your password, directly to such Social Media Service (and not to Piccing). As part of such integration, the Social Media Service will provide Piccing with access to certain information that you have provided to such Social Media Service, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and, if and to the extent applicable, the policies of such Social Media Services. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Media Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of the applicable Social Media Services provider, and, as a result, Piccing shall not have any liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Social Media Services that may be enabled within and/or otherwise accessible through the Site and/or the App.

**Security:  
**  
Piccing takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided through the Site and/or the App from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Site or through the App may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Piccing via the Internet.

**Other Terms and Conditions:**[ **  
**](http://blog.piccing.com/terms-conditions/ "Terms & Conditions")  
Your access to and use of the Site and/or the App is subject to the [Terms of Use](http://blog.piccing.com/terms-conditions/).

Changes to Piccing’s Privacy Policy: The Site, the App, and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Piccing to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Piccing reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Site and/or the App after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

**Access to Information; Contacting Piccing:  
**  
To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Site and the App.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Piccing’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Site or the App.

You may contact us as follows: [legal@piccing.com](mailto:legal@piccing.com)

**Your California Privacy Rights:  
**  
Applicable California privacy legislation permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request to access such information, please contact us as follows:  [legal@piccing.com](mailto:legal@piccing.com).

Within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.
